Muhammad Tariq Ahmad

PHP Laravel | React JS Developer



Muslim Town Lahore 54000



12-06-1995



+92-3444803459





PROFILES

Results-oriented, resourceful and problem-solving software engineer professional specializing in large scale software design and development for a wide variety of companies. High level of involvement in the advancement of the industry and adherence to best practice.

EDUCATION

GRADUATION:

Bachelor's Science in Computer Sciences Govt College University Faisalabad. With

CGPA:3.49

SKILLS

Core PHP and Framework like Laravel & CodeIgnitor

HTML,CSS,JAVASCRPT,JQUERY,BOOTSTRAP

SQL,MYSQL,Sqlite and SqlServer

Livewire , Yajra Data Table.

Third Party Integration like WooCommerce, Magento and Shopify

Version Control System GitHub and Bitbucket

Spatie Package for Role and Permission as well for user Activity log

Multi Auth System in Larave Using jetstream first party Package Sanctum.

Work as junior PHP and Laravel developer.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

10.2022 - present

Cartlow International Dubai
PHP Laravel and React developer
Working as PHP, Laravel Developer and React JS.

04.2022 - 10.2022

SourceKode Solution pvt.
Working As a PHP Laravel developer

TechBrainz Technology Pvt.
Laravel Developer
work as a PHP and Laravel developer.

09.2018 - 06.2021

Stacksea Technology Pvt.
Junior Web Developer



PROJECT DETAILS.

ReCommerce System (cartlow.com).

Working As a PHP and Laravel Framwork.

technologies Use Html,CSS and Javascript ,bootstrap and Livewire For Frontend,Media Queries

Use for Responsiveness.jquery,javascript and Mysql use for Database

https://cartlow.com

Student Management System (SMS).

Working As a Web Developer.PHP (Codeigniter,Laravel Framwork) Use for Backend,Html,CSS and Javascript and Livewire For Frontend,Media Queries

Use for Responsiveness.jquery,javascript and Mysql use for Database

https://github.com/Tariq4040/school-managemt-system-using-laravel.

Employee Management System

Using Core PHP and PHP Laravel framework for backend and Html,CSS, Javascript and Bootstrap For Frontend, Media Queries

Use for Responsiveness.jquery, and MySQL use for Database.

Hungryforjobs

Using PHP and PHP Laravel framework for backend and Html,CSS , Javascript and Bootstrap For Frontend, Media Queries

Use for Responsiveness.jquery, and MySQL use for Database.

www.hungryforjobs

Warehouse Management System (WMS)

(WMS based on multiple store integration like amazon, WooCommerce, Shopify and Magento)

Working As a Web Developer.PHP Laravel Framework Use for Backend,Html,CSS, Javascript and Bootstrap,AJAX,JSON and Livewire and Yajra For Frontend, Media Queries

Use for Responsiveness.jquery,and MySQL use for Database.

